Hope this doesn't embarrass you Jen,
but I found the best thing to do
with the new employee
is to size them up
with a long hard stare.
- So!
- So.
- First day!
- Yes!
- Scary...?
- Yes...
- Don't be scared!
- Oh I'm not really scared.
You should be!
- Well I'm a little bit scared.
- What? Don't be!
Make up your mind!
So here you are!
Yes.
I'm... really looking forward to...
- getting to grips with the...
- I'm gonna put you in I.T.
Because you said on your CV you had
a lot of experience with computers.
I did say that on my CV yes.
I have lots of experience
with the whole...
computer... thing you know, e-mails...
sending e-mails, receiving e-mails,
deleting e-mails...
- ... I could go on.
- Do!
The Web... Using mouse...
mices... using mice.
Clicking... double clicking...
the computer screen of course,
the keyboard...
the...bit that goes on the floor
down there...
- The hard drive?
- Correct.
Well, you certainly seem
to know your stuff.
That settles.
Got a good feeling about you Jen!
And they need a new manager.
Oh fantastic!
So... the people I'll be working with,
what're they like?
Standard nerds!
Hello I.T.?
Have you tried turning it off
and on again?
OK, well, the button on the side,
is it glowing?
Yeah, you need to turn it on!
The button, turns it on?!
Yeah... You... Yeah...
You do know how a button works,
don't you?
No, not on clothes!
Hello, I.T.?
Yeah?
Have you tried forcing
an unexpected reboot?
No, no! There you go! No there you go,
I just heard it come on.
No no, that's the music you hear
when it comes on.
No, that's the music you hear when...
I'm sorry, are you from the past?!
See the driver hooks a function
by patching the system call table.
So it's not safe to unload it,
unless another thread's about
to jump in there and do its stuff.
... and you don't want to end up
in middle of invalid memory.
Hello?
Oh really? Really, why don't you come
down here and make me then?
What? Oh you think I'm afraid of you?
I'm not afraid of you!
You can come down here any time
and I'll be waiting for ya!
That told her!
Oh God, it's about time you got back,
it's been all go.
You had a job?
Girl on fifth...
Did you and her... hit it off?
Define "hit it off"?
Did she continue talking to you
once you'd fixed her computer?
No...
And while I was working on it,
she rested a cup on my back.
- No?!
- Yep!
Unbelievable!
Yeah, I mean they've not respect for us
up there, no respect whatsoever!
We're all just drudgens to them.
Yes!
If there were such a thing as a drudgen,
that is what we'd be to them.
It's like they're pally-wally
when there's a problem
with their printer
but once it's fixed...
They toss us away like yesterday's jam!
Yes!
Yesterday's jam!
That is what we are to them!
Actually you know what?
That doesn't really work as a thing...
because you know, jam lasts for ages...
Hello, I.T. ?
Have you tried turning it off
and on again?
Unisex toilets? You have unisex toilets,
like Ally McBeal?
That's the sort of place this is, Jen.
A lot of sexy people not doing
much work... and having affairs.
Oh my God! Look at that view!
I feel like I'm on top of the world.
Well  Jen, this is where I leave you.
Floor 34.
Great sir, thank you.
OK. Where am I going?
All... the way down to the basement.
Good luck!
Get out of the lift...
- Oh. Won't be a tick!
- Oh my God!
Oh my God! Oh God! OK.
Hello?
Yes I believe it was Tolstoy who said...
Oh, it seems we have a visitor.
I'm sorry, myself and Morris
were just engaged
in quite a serious discussion
about books and such.
We didn't hear you come in.
Wait a second, you said it was
Tolstoy, he said what?
Oh never mind that now, Morris!
When have you read Tolstoy?
Shut up, Morris!
Why are you speaking that weird voice?
When did... I don't remember
this conversation at all!
Don't... don't let me disturb you,
I just wanted to come down....
Don't be silly you never dist...
Many people come down here to visit!
What are you talking about?
Who comes down? What people?
Why are you giving me
the secret signal to shut up?!
So... What can we do you for?
I'm the new head of this department.
Is this my office?
Why? What did she... Did she just say...
- I am the head of this department!
- I thought I was.
It's  one of us! Certainly not her!
I'm gonna sort this out...
Roy! You've got a head wound there...
Head wound!
Hi!
I don't wanna be rude or anything
but I wasn't informed of any changes
to this department.
Oh, did they not tell you about me?
N o!
And we are perfectly fine down here,
thank you very much,
we're more than capable
of taking care of ourselves.
Sure... sure...
You know you're covered in blood?
Moss!
Amazon thingy.
Ah! Wicked!
I know what this is.
It's the new Harry Potter.
I got the child edition
and the adult edition
just to check that there are
no differences in the text.
Sorry but I'm not gonna be able
to deal with that woman!
Is nobody else going to get the phone?
I suppose I'll get it!
No, that is not a phone.
I'm gonna have a little lie down.
Come in!
Yeah, Denholm. Yeah, yeah.
No no no... No they've been fine so far.
Yeah. I think we're gonna get on great.
Yeah, I know.
All right then, now you take care.
All right, yeah I will, yeah.
Ok!
Ok, take care, take care!
Ok bye! Bye!
Oh, so, hello!
What can I do you fo...
What can I do for you?
Hello. I was just wondering...
Do you want me to connect up your phone?
No no no... No.
It's working.
I was just talking to Denholm.
But how?!
Oh do you mind... Do you mind
closing the door for me?
- Oh yeah, sure.
- Yeah, Ok.
Yeah. From the other side...
Of course.
- Like this?
- That's it!
- With me on the...
- Thanks!
Are you all right?
Oh yes, Moss, I'm fine!
The nurse said I didn't do myself
any serious damage.
I'm standing over here!
I know, I know, I'm joking, I'm fine!
What we gonna do about her?
Well, I just went in, and she was having
a pretend conversation.
- Really?
- Yes.
She's a little bit weird...
to say the least.
What's that?
Oh just water.
Sometimes, I get a hot ear,
and this helps cool it down.
She is quite the oddbod...
Did you notice how
she didn't even get excited
when she saw this original ZX-IT 1?
Yeah, that was weird.
It's almost as if she doesn't know
anything about computers.
What?!
Look what you did!
Oh don't worry that's why
I always make 2 cups of tea.
Anyway, what were we talking about?
Oh, her not knowing anything
about computers.
What?!
"Dear sir, stroke, madam."
"Fire!" Exclamation mark.
"Help me!" Exclamation mark.
"123, Carendon Road."
"Looking forward to hearing from you!"
"All the best, Morris Moss."
The IT Crowd continues next!
I definitely want to get rid of her.
I agree yeah.
Ok, so, here's the plan:
A plan? Let me put on
my slightly larger glasses.
Ok, hit me!
- Ok. We go in...
- When?
You know, like in a minute.
Will that be enough time for me
to get to know the plan?
Yeah, you know what?
I shouldn't have used the word "plan"!
I... I've clearly gotten you
over-excited!
Would "steamed" be a better word?
Although that's just as exciting,
I might even use these.
All I was gonna say was...
We go in, I make up a load of bullocks
about computers
and we'll see if she picks up on it.
Yes. I can see why
you didn't want to use the word "plan".
Let me do the talk.
All right.
Ouh, Moss, Moss Moss!
Ok, we need to get this right, you know?
We... we need to stay calm.
We do not wanna go in there half-cocked.
Hang on, guys.
How can I help?
Well, we were just wondering
now that you're "The Boss",
would you like us to access
the data supplier
and connect you up to the matrix?
You just made all that up?
You don't know anything
about computers, admit it!
Will you stop trying to undermine me!
Now get in there,
and do some work, to do with computers!
I'll be in there in a minute
and check up on you!
Ok, lady!
You've won this round, but we can wait!
You will slip up one day,
and believe you me,
we will be there when you do!
There will be some piece of evidence
that will prove
without  any shadow of a doubt
that you don't know
anything about computers.
What are you doing?
Plugging in your computer.
It might be something you say...
or something you do!
But when we notice this,
and believe me we will notice this,
there's gonna be a long way down
for you, sweet chicks!
He'll realise in a second...
I cannot believe you're going
to tell on me.
You're like a pair of horrible
old women.
What did she say?
She said we're like horrible old women.
She didn't!
Hey guys!
Ok, got something to tell me?
Yes, well, it's like this:
Look at you! My I.T. Team.
- Yeah.
- Team players each and every one of you.
Yeah, what she...
There's no room for people
who can't act in a team on my team!
Excuse me.
Hello?
What?!
Well if you can't work as a team,
you're all fired!
That's it, you heard me, fine!
Get your things and go!
Hello, Security?
Everyone on floor 4 is fired.
Escort them from the premises.
And do it as a team!
Remember you're a team, and if you can't
act as a team, you're fired too!
Dawn!
Get onto recruitment.
Tell them to look for a security team
that can work as team.
They may have to escort our
security team from the building,
for not acting like a team!
Team! Team team team team team!
I even love saying the word "team".
You probably think that's a picture
of my family?
It's the A-Team.
Body, Doyle, Tiger, the Jewellery Man!
All of them!
So what do you wanna tell me?
Well, it's just not working out.
- He's joking!
- But you said...
Not working out?
Oh no! No!
We are getting on like
a big house on fire!
- Yeah!
- My ear's getting hot!
No... You know what?
We should leave, now, because
you know, you're a busy man
and we've taken far too much
of your time.
Jen could you just get the door
for me there?
Absolutely Roy!
So why did you come here
in the first place?
We set up a voice activation system
on your computer.
I  think you're gonna enjoy it.
It might just take a little while
to get the pitch right on the voice
but nonetheless, go ahead!
Thank you very much!
- Bye bye!
- Thank you!
How exciting!
Hello...
Hello computer!
Hello!
Hello... Hello computer...
What good are you?
You obviously don't know anything
about computers.
No but... OK.
But I can learn.
You know, I mean, for example Moss,
you could take me through
what you're doing right now.
I'd be delighted!
I'm just working on a very simple piece
of programming code.
I see...
Oh God, no, I'm lying again!
I didn't understand any of that!
I don't know anything
about computers, I mean...
I'm absolutely useless to you.
I might as well pack up and go home.
Hi! Is... Roy around?
Hello there little lady!
Are you lost?
How can I help you? I'm Roy.
You wanted me to come down?!
Well here I am!!
Not the face!!
Well maybe this will teach you
to treat people with
a little bit of respect!
Is it 'cos we spoke on the phone
earlier?
Oh my God! Are those Manolo's?
Yes!
They are gorgeous! Were they expensive?
No, no no no! Got them in a sale.
Oh God! Clever you!
I'm never lucky enough
to get a bargain myself.
Well, I should take you shopping.
Yeah, no that would be fantastic.
Oh I will give you a call.
Nice to meet you! Take care!
- Nice meeting you!
- Chairman! Wow!
You just diffuse that entire situation!
What situation?
Oh oh, that.. yeah!
Oh my God, does that happen a lot?
They're fairly regular,
the beatings, yes.
I'd say we're on a by-weekly beatings.
Ah it's not all that bad!
Ah, come on Roy! It's pretty bad...
Maybe I could help with this.
You know, I mean...
I'm a people person and...
people like you need a person
to deal with people...
a people person like me. Oh my God!
Ideas are coming!
Things are happening here!
Ok, Ok, what would you say here,
if I told you that I had a plan
to raise your profile upstairs by 100%.
What would you say?
I can't be done! You're crazy!
What would you say Roy?
Roy's passed out! Ok!
I need a felt-tip pen, and some paper.
PARTY - I.T. DEPT 5.45 TODAY
No no! Oh no, really really really,
that was a true story!
Unbelievable!
I said why we don't go out
with the I.T. guys more often?
- You're hilarious!
- Yes we are!
You guys should come down here
more often you know,
you should see this as a new era
for Reynholm Industries.
"A new era for Reynholm Industries!"
Oh Do you know what! If you want
to hear something really funny,
a really funny story,
you should hear what happened
to Moss and I,
when we were so drunk in Amsterdam
that Moss lost his glasses!
Moss! Moss!
Come here! Come here!
Tell them that story about
when we were drunk in Amsterdam.
Really?
Yeah yeah yeah! Oh it's brilliant!
Oh this a great story,
you're gonna love it!
I'm just gonna get another box of wine!
Well go on, then.
All right.
- Well, one night, we were really drunk.
- Yeah.
And huh, we were so drunk
that we decided to hire prostitutes.
And when they arrived to the hotel,
we were too scared to do anything,
so we brought them to the fair.
Oh really nice! In the end,
they only charged us half.
But we did have to pay
for all the rides.
Oh isn't that just the best story?
Oh, man!
You told me to never tell that story
to anyone.
Well,  what're you talking about?
That's a brilliant story!
And then you nearly walked
into the canal!
Has it got to that part
with the boatman?
Do you mean the story
when I lost my glasses?
Yes!
What story did you think I mean?
Moss?
What did you say?! What did you say?!
It's all right for you two.
You're used to being social social piranhas...
I'm a very popular person usually.
That girl earlier, that tried
to beat me to death with her shoes,
did anybody get her number?
That was a nice day the fair, wasn't it?
With Brandy and Crystal!
Hello I.T.?
Yeah. Have you tried turning it off
and on again?
Hello ! Hello !