but I found the best thing to do
with the new employee
is to size them up
with a long hard stare.
- So!
- So.
- First day!
- Yes!
- Scary...?
- Yes...
- Don't be scared!
- Oh I'm not really scared.
You should be!
- Well I'm a little bit scared.
- What? Don't be!
Make up your mind!
So here you are!
Yes.
I'm... really looking forward to...
- getting to grips with the...
- I'm gonna put you in I.T.
Because you said on your CV you had
a lot of experience with computers.
I did say that on my CV yes.
I have lots of experience
with the whole...
computer... thing you know, e-mails...
sending e-mails, receiving e-mails,
deleting e-mails...
- ... I could go on.
- Do!
The Web... Using mouse...
mices... using mice.
Clicking... double clicking...
the computer screen of course,
the keyboard...
the...bit that goes on the floor
down there...